=The Truth (Season 4)=
(New bonus scenes)
(The Listening Comprehension Test)
It's just those two organizations.
Actually, three organizations now.
One is Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
One is The Touch Today Group,
and that's useless.
Why is he the boss?
With two idiot underlings.
What if they're my underlings?
(Ke being blunt)
Your organization is the weakest.
There are only three of you.
Those two underlings have already
been taken out.
Yeah, he might be.
Who is he?
He should be
from the Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
With you guys.
You're from Kuang Kingdom.
You know that, right?
He has three underlings in total.
One of them
is with Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
And one boss is still here.
Okay.
(He's an ally)
So he's here to help us.
Your status now
(Ning starts roasting)
is the lowest in our group.
I'm telling you.
(That hit a nerve)
Mad Dragon.
(Scared me)
Proudblood, Ruthless Duke, Mad Dragon.
What?
What are you saying?
(He doesn't get it)
Speak a little louder.
No.
There's no volume control.
(Waiting)
Proudblood, Ruthless Duke, Mad Dragon.
Please respond.
What move toward?
(Can't make out the words)
Please respond.
(Jin's conclusion)
It's like those English listening tests.
(I totally get it)
(Auction warm-up)
The auction is about to start.
Does this look familiar to you?
The king's emblem
(Listen to Yang)
from the Kuang, Tui, and Li Kingdoms.
Everyone, please take your seats.
Our auction is about to begin.
We'll hand out your bidding numbers.
(Watching closely)
(Jin doesn't get it)
Why are you keep looking at me?
(Don't break character)
That's my character. Don't ruin it.
Your character is supposed
to stare at him
or stare at me?
(All in)
To stare at everyone.
(Staring)
I didn't recognize you in this look.
(Shy)
(Sweetly saying the most ruthless thing)
Full bid.
(We found a pro)
You even know what "full bid" means?
You ancient woman.
(Suspicious)
Are you really saying "full bid"?
(Almost broke character)
(Starts swinging the sword
around after getting it)
(Nice stuff)
(Let me play with it)
(Interesting)
(Playing with the sword)
(Just warming up)
(Sword showtime. He takes the stage)
(Playing along)
Thousand-Faced Eagle King
only has you three.
You too.
(Puts away sword)
I'm not with you.
(Sword)
What's the mission?
On the day of the auction,
(Seriously listening to Ning)
we need to get
(Reasoning and swordplay)
those three treasures.
(Little skit begins)
(Ready, Ding?)
(Bring it, He)
(Playing along)
(Ding goes dark)
(I'm fighting back)
(Here comes the chance)
(Sneak attack)
The killer's gone crazy.
(Sword back with Ke)
(Strike a pose)
(Smooth as silk)
(The familiar ID is back)
Wait. I have a question.
Only the two of us
are members of this organization.
So we've narrowed it down
to two people now.
He's not one of them?
(I'm not, I'm not)
I'm not.
But he could pretend to be
someone from Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
(Taking it seriously)
He could tell him he's from the group.
Look at our group members.
Yeah, because that person
is from the group.
He sent me the message.
Exactly.
So twenty people in your group
(Key point)
share the same information.
I'm not even in the organization.
(Desperately proving his innocence)
How could I have messaged her?
(Sees through everything)
There is Proudblood,
Ruthless Duke, Mad Dragon.
Am I really in the group?
I am
Thunder, the Supreme Phantom Dragonlord.
(Dragonlord becomes a potato)
You must be Potato.
Sorry.
(Potato herself)
I just really like potatoes.
Which one are you?
I'm Mad Dragon.
My name
is Proudblood,
Ruthless Duke, Mad Dragon.
(Officially lost her memory)
I've forgotten who I am.
(Blueberry lover)
Do we have blueberries?
You're princess.
You're Princess Donasia
Ronaswa Ulala, right?
I am
Princess Donasia Ronaswa Ulala.
Who am I?
Proudblood Mad Dragon.
(You got it wrong)
I'm Mad Dragon.
You must be Sweet Potato.
I'm not Sweet Potato.
Genius Boy.
He's Genius Boy.
Lanalan Lunalan Genius Boy.
You're princess.
(Everyone remembers now)
Princess is Sun Qian.
Helpful Contact.
Who's Helpful Contact?
He's been undercover this whole time.
I think that's right.
Because the two of us have
our own IDs (identities).
Except the one pretending
to stay undercover.
(Look me in the eyes)
(Pressing closer)
Isn't this you?
Wait, Leggy McShy,
(Finally caught you)
Kinda Awkward, Innocent Hunk.
Isn't this you?
(Still denying it)
I am
Leggy McShy,
Kinda Awkward, Innocent Hunk.
(One more jab)
You were quick to clear yourself.
(Caught red-handed)
You were just trying to deny it.
I don't know!
I don't know.
(Number one troublemaker)
Are you a little rabbit?
You don't know anything.
(The ice cream they can't forget)
There's ice cream in the back.
(Foodie is on the hunt)
I'll see if I can get some.
Okay.
(On the hunt for food)
Zhang Jiawei is looking for food again.
He's just that hungry.
He told me, "Hold the mic for me."
"I'll see if I can get some ice cream."
(Exact replica)
Zhang Jiawei.
I can't open it.
(Came up empty-handed)
The fridge is locked
(I thought you were just kidding)
You really are looking for food?
Yeah, there's a fridge back here.
It's full of ice cream.
What's this key for?
Is there anything here it can open?
Well, Curator Tui.
There's a fridge in the back.
(Been thinking about it nonstop)
It's full of ice cream.
(Foodie joins the hunt)
Let's find some ice cream.
(Foodie +1) I want some too.
I can't open it.
(Feeling wronged)
It's locked.
What's locked?
(Be honest)
There's a fridge in the back.
(Let me look)
What are you doing?
(I know)
She's going to look for food.
(Came up empty-handed +1)
Let's go, everyone.
Well, you can get some sleep.
Pull the blanket over you.
Rest for a bit before you go.
Get some sleep.
(Always on my mind)
There's ice cream over there.
You can have some.
(Can't forget it)
You can grab some for us too.
(Still thinking about it)
Grab some for us.
Let's go.
Longdong Army.
Longdong Army!
It kind of sounds
like "Crayon Shin-chan".
=The Truth (Season 4)=
(SVIP updates Wed & Thu at 12PM.)
(VIP updates next day at 12PM,
one week early.)